Good morning
Today is the last day of our
agentic coding training squad 2
20 participants are graduating and
I just thought of three
tips for sustained performance
and learning in
the agentic era First tip is that
join the community be active in
discord server
or groups or meetups
and so on Second tip is
share your screen If you share
your screen you get so much feedback
and from other people they
are very open to helping you
And third because working with agents
can be really overwhelming
you should take a walk after an
exhaustive session That
really helps me to clarify my thinking
and gather the thoughts Hope
this helps